<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Having tenants for breakfast</title>
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast" />
    <updated>2021-10-08T20:58:39+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>The Breakfaster</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast</id>

    <entry>
        <title>I want either the world or my sexual and other drives to shut up and leave me alone.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-want-either-the-world-or-my-sexual-and-other-drives-to-shut-up-and-leave-me-alone.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-want-either-the-world-or-my-sexual-and-other-drives-to-shut-up-and-leave-me-alone.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:58:39+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I often find myself do nothing. The reason is simple: whatever I could do, I read as many pros as I read cons for activities. And it's a never ending stream of data that could or could not be true. For instance, finances. The problem&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I often find myself do nothing. The reason is simple: whatever I could do, I read as many pros as I read cons for activities.<br>And it's a never ending stream of data that could or could not be true. <br><br>For instance, finances.</p>
<ul>
<li>Shares, yes or no? Well, it depends on X, but if you do Y remember Z.</li>
<li>Daytrading. Not working/working. Blahblahblah.</li>
<li>ETFs. Awesome idea or Worst idea you could have</li>
</ul>
<p>The problem is as mentioned always the same: it is all opinions. And they all involve risks.<br><br>Nothing is for certain. Nothing is proven.<br><br>Trying it out can ruin you. Survivorship bias anyone?<br><br>"Has it ever worked for anyone?" is what I always wonder?<br><br>All the information(not knowledge) drives me insane.<br><br>Don't even get me started on pickup literature.<br><br>TRY OUT NEW THINGS. Yeah, right. I did, it did not work, what now, WHO THE FUCK DO I TALK TO NOW?<br><br>If I post in forums, the ones responsible for advice don't answer, but people who are quick to say "Why did you do that in the first place, of course it didn't work".<br><br>I want a way out of this shit. <br><br>Just like pickup. So many things don't work in pickup. So just stopping it leads to what? My reptilian brain wants to have sex. So that doesn't work. And rubbing one out is not sufficient for it. And the cycle repeats.<br><br>I want either the world or my sexual and other drives to shut up and leave me alone.<br><br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>I was walking on the streets today and there was some street festival going on. I noticed some things.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-was-walking-on-the-streets-today-and-there-was-some-street-festival-going-on-i-noticed-some-things.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-was-walking-on-the-streets-today-and-there-was-some-street-festival-going-on-i-noticed-some-things.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:57:58+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     If you smile, you open up, why should I open myself to random strangers? It hurts even more to then get rejected. I stay behind my protection. I feel great walking angryly through a street festival with fake smiling women who stop smiling once&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
<li>If you smile, you open up, why should I open myself to random strangers? It hurts even more to then get rejected. I stay behind my protection. I feel great walking angryly through a street festival with fake smiling women who stop smiling once they see my stern face for them to feel worse afterwards.</li>
<li>If they don't look, they are busy with their mobile phone, are in a hurry, look disconnected - they don't even want to connect to strangers.</li>
<li>Women ignored me when I was younger, never helped me improve then I found pickup and all pickup does is endorse this behaviour of them. "Reward her for ignoring you, this is the new weapon of men against feminists! Kiss her ass better than other men, then you will get sex." What is wrong with the world?</li>
<li>Beautiful women always have a boyfriend but they offer nothing in return yet every man not having a woman is seen a failure.</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>It gives me pleasure going on a date with a woman, not making any &quot;move&quot;, waiting for her to get more and more frustrated to then leave and delete her contact details</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/it-gives-me-pleasure-going-on-a-date-with-a-woman-not-making-any-move-waiting-for-her-to-get-more-and-more-frustrated-to-then-leave-and-delete-her-contact-details.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/it-gives-me-pleasure-going-on-a-date-with-a-woman-not-making-any-move-waiting-for-her-to-get-more-and-more-frustrated-to-then-leave-and-delete-her-contact-details.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:57:25+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I do this because of the amount of resentment for being degraded to certain "acceptable" behaviour. Not showing this behaviour, not taking risks of rejection just for her, not being her fucking prince charming, gives me great liberation. And seeing her suffer because of it&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I do this because of the amount of resentment for being degraded to certain "acceptable" behaviour. Not showing this behaviour, not taking risks of rejection just for her, not being her fucking prince charming, gives me great liberation. And seeing her suffer because of it makes me happy. In a few hours I'll have another date. I hope I can make her suffer that way. The only thing that matters is holding the frame.<br><br>Can you relate?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>It seems as if everything we’ve ever read on the subject prepares us for interactions with beautiful but bitchy women, who are typically saturated with “bothersome” male attention and are therefore eager to reject us.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/it-seems-as-if-everything-weve-ever-read-on-the-subject-prepares-us-for-interactions-with-beautiful-but-bitchy-women-who-are-typically-saturated-with-bothersome-male-attention-and-are-therefore-eager-to-reject-us.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/it-seems-as-if-everything-weve-ever-read-on-the-subject-prepares-us-for-interactions-with-beautiful-but-bitchy-women-who-are-typically-saturated-with-bothersome-male-attention-and-are-therefore-eager-to-reject-us.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:57:15+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I read this quote on some website. This is exactly how it is. I just experienced it today again. I was genuinely in a hurry because I had to get out the next bus stop. And there she was. So I went over, said I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I read this quote on some website. <br><br>This is exactly how it is. I just experienced it today again. I was genuinely in a hurry because I had to get out the next bus stop. And there she was. So I went over, said I had to leave at the next stop but found her quite attractive. I then told her to give me something to contact her(because I had no time for the DO-YOU-HAVE-FACEBOOK-NO-GIVE-ME-YOUR-NUMBER-OH-YOU-DON'T-GIVE-YOUR-NUMBER-TO-STRANGERS-YES-YOU-SHOULDN'T-GIVE-ME-YOUR-NUMBER-I-CAN-BE-DANGEROUS Time-wasting). She leaned back, smiled and said with a cocky tone "I am taken". She must have missed the "I have to get out at the next stop" part. So the next stop came and I left the bus.<br>How can you not hate women for that? Not being able to approach to then value someone not even being there higher than you while you have no time dealing with that shit.<br>And this is how most women behave.<br><br>Also I would LOVE to know how to put women down properly instead of being "more mature". Fuck maturity. Children even fuck each other. Having sex as an adult with an adult is still fucking and there is no maturity necessary.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jokes about Hitler show fear of Hitler</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/jokes-about-hitler-show-fear-of-hitler.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/jokes-about-hitler-show-fear-of-hitler.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:57:01+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There is a kind of joke that never dies: the nazi joke. Mocking hitler. Mocking the SS. Mocking the Gestapo. There are games about this time. A lot of books. But in the end, people are severely terrified. This is their coping mechanism. If Hitler&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>There is a kind of joke that never dies: the nazi joke.<br><br>Mocking hitler. Mocking the SS. Mocking the Gestapo.<br><br>There are games about this time. A lot of books.<br><br>But in the end, people are severely terrified. This is their coping mechanism.<br><br>If Hitler was alive today, those people joking would say nothing.<br><br>It's like mocking the army. The army gets respect because there are repercussions for not respecting them.<br><br>Ultimately people being against Hitler just feel safe in their societaly echo chamber bubble. They are through and through opportunists, who would raise their hands and scream "Heil" in a heartbeat if another Hitler came to power.<br><br>Just like they wear their facemasks like the tough warriors that they are.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jordan Petersen and being less naive</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/jordan-petersen-and-being-less-naive.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/jordan-petersen-and-being-less-naive.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:56:48+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     I recently heard him say in his kermit voice close to tears that being married was very important and the older you got, the worse it got to rely on someone. Therefore, to not be alone later, you had to get and stay married.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
<li>I recently heard him say in his kermit voice close to tears that being married was very important and the older you got, the worse it got to rely on someone. Therefore, to not be alone later, you had to get and stay married. He was also quite dismissive about mgtow but later he showed compassion.</li>
<li>Then he talks about standing up for yourself and saying what is right for you, basically going your own way.</li>
</ol>
<p><br>Re 1.: There is something to it. Not the married part, but the being alone part. I notice that I was often taken advantage of because of this desire for companionship. If people were not nice to me and all of a sudden were nice to me(to play me for a fool) I was always hooked. "Oh someone is nice to me I am so grateful". I could punch my naive being in the face for being so easily manipulated. I also resonate with Petersen when he talks about naivety. Unfortunately he offers no solution against being naive (and therefore traumatized when being mistreated) other than "accepting malevolence" in people. Which is not changing anyones mind. He also talks about how fighting with your siblings is good. But what if you don't win, but always lose? Where is the manual for children on how to fight back, if they don't get it themselves?<br><br>Back in the day I remember just minding my own business and people always came and wanted to mess with me. I didn't do shit to them. Everybody around me(mostly women) told me that "they were just stupid", nobody said: "Dude, you go to martial arts next monday. And then you face your bully. End of discussion.".<br><br>Today I hear about people telling me they have constant headaches because of martial arts. One of the better known ones is Joe Rogen.<br><br>So not even martial arts helps. And I don't get weapons to defend myself.<br><br>So I couldn't rely on my emotions, so I tried to detach myself from the desire to be liked as pickup teaches. It was a fight against windmills. I couldn't rewire my brain. And once I let go of my efforts, I was again the helpless defenseless little creature I have always been.<br><br>What could I do?<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Nothing is worth being learnt</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/nothing-is-worth-being-learnt.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/nothing-is-worth-being-learnt.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:55:41+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I am sick of learning. Sick of step one, two, three. Whenever I see a book about How to do X, I think Why? It is tedious, I have to focus and ultimately I am going to die anyway and everything was in vain. For&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I am sick of learning. Sick of step one, two, three.<br>Whenever I see a book about How to do X, I think Why?<br>It is tedious, I have to focus and ultimately I am going to die anyway and everything was in vain. For instance i recently saw a book about quadrocopters. How to take photos with them. And this idiot writer started with shit like aperture size, of course after he talked about how awesome he was and which prices this fool won. As if I cared.<br>BTT. Photos are photos. They have a purpose. They should show something, not show it well. Why should I invest time and learn this shit? In the end, all I get are photos. Press a trigger and you have them. Fly a drone, press buttons. None of it deserves trees to be killed for. End of it.<br>It transcends to basically every topic. Fighting? Why should I learn how to fight. I die anyways, why defend myself? Also if I defend myself I go to jail, so why even bother? If I even make it that far and not die from brain trauma due to "sparring". All those fags going to university to learn something. For what? For motherfucking what? Money? Fame? <br>Or Pickup. Step 12345. Remember all of them. The arrogance teachers have as in "you know shit and I am going to tell you how to think". Nothing is worth being learnt.<br>I am going to burn all books I once bought. I am going to delete all ebooks. No value in those shitty steponetwothree fucks, only a waste of time.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pickup does not contradict MGTOW, because both has the same roots</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/pickup-does-not-contradict-mgtow-because-both-has-the-same-roots.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/pickup-does-not-contradict-mgtow-because-both-has-the-same-roots.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:55:29+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pickup does not contradict MGTOW, because both have the same roots Pickup is a set of tools meant to have sex with a woman you fancy. MGTOW is about not marrying a woman and staying true to your desires. What I hate about every pickup&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>Pickup does not contradict MGTOW, because both have the same roots</strong><br><br>Pickup is a set of tools meant to have sex with a woman you fancy. MGTOW is about not marrying a woman and staying true to your desires.<br><br>What I hate about every pickup forum out there is the condescending tone people have. "That sucks". They would never say that. No sympathy, empathy, nothing. Only insults and "go out more you fag" - kind of tone.<br><br>I came to the conclusion that I did not need much of pickup literature.<br><br>What I needed was dealing with my past. With past mental trauma. I recently started writing down trauma that I remember. Everytime a new traumatic memory comes up, j'écris. A lot of mistreatment comes up that I experienced. Once I find new approaches to each, new ones come up. But that's a good thing, because it means I am moving forward.<br><br>I feel bad currently. And that's good. Because it's an openly bad feeling. Not suppressed bad, but open bad. I come closer to resolving more and more issues and boy there are many.<br><br>I thought it was some major traumatic events in my life, but no, those are on par with many others.<br><br>Men often say that women betrayed them. And they did. The question is: what did those men do to allow women do this?<br><br>This again, is a good thing. If I know what I did, I can change the future.<br><br>So to go my own way, I have to be happy to remember traumatic memories.<br><br>If new ones come up, it means that others that were more dominant fade.<br><br>The stress when talking to women, the pain when they betray you. You, in general, wondering "why do I do this". It all is in your past trauma.<br><br>Thus we should deal with trauma. Then pickup is going up to a woman and saying hi.<br><br>It is my theory that creepy men are just men who want one thing, have sex with women.<br><br>Their traumatic experiences, fear and tightness, prevent them from being confident around women.<br><br>I know it's unfair that others don't have that much trauma or ptsd most of us have. That they have it easier.<br><br>It is how it is.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Receiving 433 Mhz signal</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/receiving-433-mhz-signal.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/receiving-433-mhz-signal.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:55:08+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    My goal is to use my wireless 433 Mhz doorbell signal to send an email once someone rings. Now my problem is how to intercept the doorbell signal, it's probably encoded to not interfere with other 433 Mhz signals. Can I use https://www.amazon.de/Neuftech-Wireless-Module-Transceiver-externen/dp/B01CI01F94 for this on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>My goal is to use my wireless 433 Mhz doorbell signal to send an email once someone rings.<br><br>Now my problem is how to intercept the doorbell signal, it's probably encoded to not interfere with other 433 Mhz signals.<br><br>Can I use <a href="https://www.amazon.de/Neuftech-Wireless-Module-Transceiver-externen/dp/B01CI01F94" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.amazon.de/Neuftech-Wireless-Module-Transceiver-externen/dp/B01CI01F94</a> for this on rpi?<br><br>Or does the rpi have the opportunity to already receive 433 Mhz, after all, it can emit radio frequencies using gpio using pifmrds in the Mhz area, can this be reversed to act as a receiver without additional hardware?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Something is wrong with qualification</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/something-is-wrong-with-qualification.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/something-is-wrong-with-qualification.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:53:44+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    According to pickup, shortly before I approach a woman coldly, I should be happy and smile. She is very attractive and looks up and down at me when approaching in disgust. How should I maintain a good mood then? In this moment I think: "I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>According to pickup, shortly before I approach a woman coldly, I should be happy and smile.<br>She is very attractive and looks up and down at me when approaching in disgust.<br>How should I maintain a good mood then?<br>In this moment I think: "I am doing you a favour by approaching you, girl. But it seems that you don't honour that!". Then I think "Why do I not also build up an "assholeshield", look condescendingly at her and say something even more derogatory to put her down?"<br>So you shouldn't give her a stern look, because that's creepy?<br>I should care about her not being creeped out? Does she? Does she care about me feeling good? Why should I?<br>And there it goes. No conversation, nothing.<br>But I looked more and more at couples and realized how unhappy those men were. ESPECIALLY those with children.<br>If walking around expecting something good to happen, women just drag me down further. Like going to a friend greeting him and he says "Go fuck yourself, I will never talk to you again" hits you way more than a "Go fuck yourself" from your enemy after you put him down. If on the other hand I expect rejection and go in expecting a fight, the first attack of her like a boyfriend does not hit me, I have my shield up.<br>How can a human being looking at you with aggression deserve your kindness because this human being has a vagina?<br>I don't understand why you should smile and make a woman's day. For what? Putting you down? Telling you about her boyfriend? Why waste your time?<br>But using negs made some women become resentful, others viewed it as a game and tried to up the ante. It has never led to sex.<br>But just saying "Hey, I think you are attractive, what's your name" leads nowhere either, except right to the boyfriend line.<br>So whatever I do, be honest or condescending-hateful, the ones I fancy never fancy me.<br>When walking outside, all I see are angry or condescending female faces.<br>If I used another approach and said: "Hmm, let's see if I like her" it would go like that - and always went like that in the past:<br>\*Some preceding conversation\*<br>Me: Hey, what do you do for a living?<br>She: "I am studying Y"<br>I don't care about Y. She failed.<br>Me: "Okay, so what do you do when you have free time?"<br>She: "I go to the cinema"<br>I think "I go skydiving and all she can do is going to the cinema"<br>My summary: a boring human being who is really attractive. But because pickup people said, she would be attracted if you liked her character and if she had to work for it, I do the stupid qualification. So I qualify her more and she fails every test.<br>But my genitals do not care. And neither do I.<br>"But hey, it is so important for her to work for it."<br>So I say: "Okay, you are not good enough for me"<br>She: "Yeah whatever"<br>We split. Great outcome. I qualifed that women, standing ovations by imaginary pickup artists.<br>In short, a woman will never pass my shittests. So why even bother qualifying her, because someone in the community said so? Really?<br>They live in this fairy tale world where there are countless available and sexy women in daygame and you could qualify.<br>Reality: most women look average or bad. Randomly there is an attractive girl. I cannot qualify her, because I want her.<br>This pickup shit drifted so far off male interests. I do not want to make her day and pamper her with a good qualifying experience.<br>Something is really wrong with qualification.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
