<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Having tenants for breakfast</title>
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast" />
    <updated>2021-10-24T15:14:18+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>The Breakfaster</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast</id>

    <entry>
        <title>About positive masculinity</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/about-positive-masculinity.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/about-positive-masculinity.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-24T15:14:18+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I saw this video My remarks: The solution is to choose the best free tutorial to then follow it. Protecting a woman and loved ones is overrated. The worst that happens to you is that a woman leaves you. And loved ones can protect themselves.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I saw this video</p>
<div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5WU7McpvxzM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>My remarks:</p>
<p>The solution is to choose the best free tutorial to then follow it. Protecting a woman and loved ones is overrated. The worst that happens to you is that a woman leaves you. And loved ones can protect themselves. He paints a picture of masculinity that does not value the man, but what he provides for others. He says "How the 5 Traits of Positive Masculinity" lead to you being valuable to others.</p>
<div>If you don't explain, you will not get new ideas by explaining. When you are wrong, you stay wrong. Yes, most people want you to explain to make you doubt yourself. But you use this opportunity for yourself. Then you are not taken advantage of.</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Don&#x27;t tell a woman to lose weight</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/dont-tell-a-woman-to-lose-weight.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/dont-tell-a-woman-to-lose-weight.html</id>
            <category term="MGTOW"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:58:02+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Relationships are mainly defined by mutual sexual attraction. It seems that many people assume women should not be told to lose weight. "Never tell a woman that she needs to lose weight" stems from women themselves. Like us saying "Approach us and treat us well".
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Relationships are mainly defined by mutual sexual attraction. It seems that many people assume women should not be told to lose weight.</p>
<p>"Never tell a woman that she needs to lose weight" stems from women themselves. Like us saying "Approach us and treat us well".</p>
<p>Do they care? Nope, not in the slightest, quite the contrary.</p>
<p>Therefore don't bother hurting her comfortable lazy feeling and value your values. Tell a woman to lose fat or lose you. And set a timeframe. Remember: once you lose your manly character in one way or another, she's gone in an instant. We are mainly about looks, which is perfectly fine. So enforce it and you will feel better.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How do you control how to react when you are under emotional distress?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/how-do-you-control-how-to-react-when-you-are-under-emotional-distress.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/how-do-you-control-how-to-react-when-you-are-under-emotional-distress.html</id>
            <category term="MGTOW"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:56:56+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You know the saying "You cannot control what people do, but you can control, how you react". How do you control how to react when you are under emotional distress? From Eckhart Tolle I know that the only thing you can do is observe. But&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know the saying "You cannot control what people do, but you can control, how you react".</p>
<p>How do you control how to react when you are under emotional distress?</p>
<p>From Eckhart Tolle I know that the only thing you can do is observe.</p>
<p>But in moments of pressure, of stress, I do not have time to observe. I need support from my body. Not some fucked up memory of the past in which I did not succeed in a similar situation.</p>
<p>Also, in my experience, you cannot "observe in advance" to then have stillness of mind when it matters.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Psyching people out who want to mess with you</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/psyching-people-out-who-want-to-mess-with-you.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/psyching-people-out-who-want-to-mess-with-you.html</id>
            <category term="martialarts"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:54:52+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So you looked a foreigner too long in his eyes according to his taste and he starts a verbal beef. You decide to put him in his place and you decide to double down on it. The situation is a supermarket in a civilized city,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So you looked a foreigner too long in his eyes according to his taste and he starts a verbal beef. You decide to put him in his place and you decide to double down on it.</p>
<p>The situation is a supermarket in a civilized city, so you cannot just start a fight there.</p>
<p>But you assume that if you don't say anything or scare him well, he'll just wait outside the supermarket because he thinks he was superior, as you looked away first.</p>
<p>How do you deescalate <strong>by doubling down</strong> on your statement to make him doubt himself and the likelyhood of an afterplay less or in any case less severe because you showed him his weakness.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How do I properly loopback/dsnoop?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/how-do-i-properly-loopbackdsnoop.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/how-do-i-properly-loopbackdsnoop.html</id>
            <category term="learnpython"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:53:19+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I am trying to record a loopback signal, ie audio playing by aplay test.wav &amp; with arecord -f cd -Dplug:dsnoop foobar.wav yet even though I hear test.wav from my speakers foobar.wav is an empty line of silence. Amplified I get regular beeps and noise in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I am trying to record a loopback signal, ie audio playing by</p>
<p><code>aplay test.wav &amp;</code></p>
<p>with</p>
<p><code>arecord -f cd -Dplug:dsnoop foobar.wav</code></p>
<p>yet even though I hear <code>test.wav</code> from my speakers <code>foobar.wav</code> is an empty line of silence. Amplified I get regular beeps and noise in between, everything but <code>test.wav</code>.</p>
<p>How do I properly loopback/dsnoop?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why I dislike Zombie Shooters</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-dislike-zombie-shooters-2.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-dislike-zombie-shooters-2.html</id>
            <category term="gaming"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:52:04+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Day Z, Dying Light, Left 4 Dead 2. They all are about killing zombies. But zombies are just infected humans. That does nothing to me emotionally. But when there is an elaborately crafted enemy as in the evil within or silent hill, I am all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Day Z, Dying Light, Left 4 Dead 2. They all are about killing zombies. But zombies are just infected humans. That does nothing to me emotionally. But when there is an elaborately crafted enemy as in the evil within or silent hill, I am all for it.<br><br>But zombies? Meh. It's like those ice princess toon that is being shoved into girls throats left and right. The creators had way too much marketing money and decided: WE WILL FORCE THE PEOPLE TO LIKE IT. The ice princess and zombies are both just stupid characters. Compare that to the batman's joker, be it in gotham or one of the movies. Now there went some work in it. But zombies.... There are hardly any games without zombies which might be the reason why people are buying that uncreative shit, might be the reason they have to pile them up because one zombie would be too obviously bland.<br><br>TL/DR: Zombies are not elaboratively crafted compared to even the simplest enemy in non-zombie games. Also, nobody asked for zombies, but as there is a lack of games, people started playing zombie games. Which made developers think people liked it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A revival of stupid irc-times.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/a-revival-of-stupid-irc-times.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/a-revival-of-stupid-irc-times.html</id>
            <category term="discordsucks"/>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:51:32+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It's like those stupid livestreams when whatever you write is never being picked up because it just goes down in the crowd of statements of others. A revival of stupid irc-times.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It's like those stupid livestreams when whatever you write is never being picked up because it just goes down in the crowd of statements of others.<br><br>A revival of stupid irc-times.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>[SERIOUS] How can you use the current pandemic financially, personally and in general - what should you do right now that you probably won&#x27;t have the option to do later, as this pandemic is probably a once in a lifetime situation?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/serious-how-can-you-use-the-current-pandemic-financially-personally-and-in-general-what-should-you-do-right-now-that-you-probably-wont-have-the-option-to-do-later-as-this-pandemic-is-probably-a-once-in-a-lifetime-situation.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/serious-how-can-you-use-the-current-pandemic-financially-personally-and-in-general-what-should-you-do-right-now-that-you-probably-wont-have-the-option-to-do-later-as-this-pandemic-is-probably-a-once-in-a-lifetime-situation.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:46:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>I am a human being. AMA.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-am-a-human-being-ama.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/i-am-a-human-being-ama.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:46:10+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mind versus Sex drive</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/mind-versus-sex-drive.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/mind-versus-sex-drive.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-09T11:45:25+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Recently I remembered that I can talk to women if I want to, that I don't have to. This relieved me a bit. Then I looked at their faces, their expressions and I realized, I don't want anything to do with a human like that.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Recently I remembered that I can talk to women if I want to, that I don't have to. This relieved me a bit. Then I looked at their faces, their expressions and I realized, I don't want anything to do with a human like that. If you look at female faces in public, they are never happy or inviting. Dismissive, angry, hateful, condescending is what I describe them.<br>They don't look at me and always pretend to be busy.<br>And I - being dressed whatever - am never good enough. Just stopping them without them rolling their eyes is very hard.<br>My sex drive has made me stay in that torture-loop of being horny and being rejected for more than 10 years now.<br>Also pickup advice made me stay there because they always say "try".</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
