<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Having tenants for breakfast</title>
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast" />
    <updated>2021-10-08T20:46:29+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>The Breakfaster</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast</id>

    <entry>
        <title>[Vote]What is your ratio between protein powder and organic protein?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/votewhat-is-your-ratio-between-protein-powder-and-organic-protein.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/votewhat-is-your-ratio-between-protein-powder-and-organic-protein.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:46:29+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Organic protein means every nutrition that has high protein and is not strongly industrially modified. Examples: Result Option 1 Text: 100% protein powder, 0% organic protein Vote Count: 10 Option 2 Text: 75% protein powder, 25% organic protein Vote Count: 11 Option 3 Text: 25%&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Organic protein means every nutrition that has high protein and is not strongly industrially modified.<br><br>Examples:</p>
<ol>
<li>Cheese</li>
<li>Meat</li>
<li>Nuts</li>
<li>Eggs</li>
<li>Fish</li>
</ol>
<p><br>Result<br><br>Option 1<br>Text: 100% protein powder, 0% organic protein<br>Vote Count: 10<br><br>Option 2<br>Text: 75% protein powder, 25% organic protein<br>Vote Count: 11<br><br>Option 3<br>Text: 25% protein powder, 75% organic protein<br>Vote Count: 50<br><br>Option 4<br>Text: 0% protein powder, 100% organic protein<br>Vote Count: 15<br><br>Total Vote Count: 86<br><br>Voting End: 2020-09-30 19:41:49<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What really gets to me is when there&#x27;s unity among others in injustice.</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/what-really-gets-to-me-is-when-theres-unity-among-others-in-injustice.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/what-really-gets-to-me-is-when-theres-unity-among-others-in-injustice.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:45:03+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Examples You write in a forum a harmless question and the first guy to reply says "Troll". Then all others chime in and say "Troll" and nobody takes you seriously. You ask, why they do this and even more say "What a troll". Once I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>Examples</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>You write in a forum a harmless question and the first guy to reply says "Troll". Then all others chime in and say "Troll" and nobody takes you seriously. You ask, why they do this and even more say "What a troll".</li>
<li>Once I asked in a forum where I can find a manual for a device. The first answer was "Here it is(link), some people cannot use google". The next answer was "Yeah, really stupid people are around today". Now the manual was not at the link destination, therefore the link was not helpful at all. So I wrote: "No, I can use google and the result is not there". Then another guy chimed in, calling me a troll. And another one said, I was so ungrateful, then the frequently used "people just tried to help" and on it went. And not a single person supporting me. I normally continue to set people straight till the mod blocks me with some arrogant statement, often containing the word "troll" aswell. Or worse, trying to tell me that I had to remain calm and let the mod handle it, when in reality he never stops others from behaving that way and always chimes in. But if I step up and stand my ground, I am immediately banned. It's like this always in so many places on the internet. As if those assholes were part of the mods making money strategy with their shitty forum.</li>
<li>Or in a subway. Some woman, not disabled or pregnant, shouts at me and tries to give commands that I had to remove my backpack next to me, so she can sit. No please, no respect, as if I was her slave. Other seats were free aswell. I told her, for her to sit, she has to ask respectfully. She starts shouting and all other people around her chime in, saying "Just let her sit there". I say it again, louder and fully ready to have a physical confrontation with every low life in the train. Dead silence. Then the first people start saying "well, you are right, her tone was way off". Those didn't say a word of encouragement before. Nothing. At least, here I can look them in the eye and make them notice that they are not anonymous and face consequences for their actions.<br><br><br></li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>When do I know that she wants me and is just playing stupid games or that she doesn&#x27;t want me and uses the group as an excuse?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-do-i-know-that-she-wants-me-and-is-just-playing-stupid-games-or-that-she-doesnt-want-me-and-uses-the-group-as-an-excuse-2.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-do-i-know-that-she-wants-me-and-is-just-playing-stupid-games-or-that-she-doesnt-want-me-and-uses-the-group-as-an-excuse-2.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:44:18+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You see a woman in a mixed set, some guys, some girls. You fancy that woman. If a woman is by herself, I just tell her that I find her attractive. Then we talk and I try to sustain attraction while moving her. If a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You see a woman in a mixed set, some guys, some girls. You fancy that woman.<br><br>If a woman is by herself, I just tell her that I find her attractive. Then we talk and I try to sustain attraction while moving her.<br><br>If a woman is in a group, some guy in the group might be into her or had sex with her.<br><br>My problem is simple. If I go up to her in a group and she wants to play hard to get as in "I don't know" after I told her that I liked her, do I just hang in there? <br><br>When something similar happened I felt like: "girl, can't you see that it's getting heated in here? Just give me an easy way out or say yes, but that shit brings me in jeopardy. I want to meet you, you hide in this group, my only way to meet you is to approach and talk to you. Show some gratitude and come with me."<br><br>Obviously a bad position to be in.<br><br>The other guys, jealous as they are, will probably say things like "Don't you see, she is not into you" and shit. <br><br>Once I did this, a woman played dumb as they always do, enjoying the inevitable competition between men. But I don't care about some other guy.<br><br>If they weren't around and she was by herself, I would just try and change her mood, move her around. But in a group, a girl resists isolation with that phrase, that would mean NOTHING if she was by herself.<br><br>So does "I find you attractive" not work in groups?<br><br>You will probably now suggest the panacea "group theory". In my experience, befriending the friends has never worked, if anything it made the woman I fancied leave with "Oh you guys seem to get along so well". Also, they are HER friends, not my friends. I CHOOSE people I hang out with and I will definitely not become friends with some guy who wants to have sex with her or wants me to leave.<br><br>So this doesn't work either.<br><br>So the question is, how to approach this situation and when do I know that she wants me and is just playing stupid games or that she doesn't want me and uses the group as an excuse?<br><br>Also I wonder should I smile or not. On the one hand, I don't want her to be in fear, but I do want the other guys to think twice if they want to mess with me.<br><br>To moralfags: I will skip your post.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>When do I know that she wants me and is just playing stupid games or that she doesn&#x27;t want me and uses the group as an excuse?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-do-i-know-that-she-wants-me-and-is-just-playing-stupid-games-or-that-she-doesnt-want-me-and-uses-the-group-as-an-excuse.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-do-i-know-that-she-wants-me-and-is-just-playing-stupid-games-or-that-she-doesnt-want-me-and-uses-the-group-as-an-excuse.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:44:05+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You see a woman in a mixed set, some guys, some girls. You fancy that woman. If a woman is by herself, I just tell her that I find her attractive. Then we talk and I try to sustain attraction while moving her. If a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You see a woman in a mixed set, some guys, some girls. You fancy that woman.<br><br>If a woman is by herself, I just tell her that I find her attractive. Then we talk and I try to sustain attraction while moving her.<br><br>If a woman is in a group, some guy in the group might be into her or had sex with her.<br><br>My problem is simple. If I go up to her in a group and she wants to play hard to get as in "I don't know" after I told her that I liked her, do I just hang in there? The other guys, jealous as they are, will probably say things like "Don't you see, she is not into you" and shit. Once I did this, a woman played dumb as they always do, enjoying the inevitable competition between men. But I don't care about some other guy. And those other guys always want to "cuddle" faggots as they are.<br><br>If they weren't around and she was by herself, I would just try and change her mood, move her around. But in a group, a girl resists isolation with that phrase, that would mean NOTHING if she was by herself.<br><br>So does "I find you attractive" not work in groups?<br><br>You will probably now suggest the panacea "group theory". In my experience, befriending the friends has never worked, if anything it made the woman I fancied leave with "Oh you guys seem to get along so well". Also, they are HER friends, not my friends. I CHOOSE people I hang out with and I will definitely not become friends with some guy who wants to have sex with her or wants me to leave.<br><br>So this doesn't work either.<br><br>So the question is, how to approach this situation and when do I know that she wants me and is just playing stupid games or that she doesn't want me and uses the group as an excuse?<br><br>Also I wonder should I smile or not. On the one hand, I don't want her to be in fear, but I do want the other guys to think twice if they want to mess with me.<br><br>To moralfags: I will skip your post.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>When I am happy, people treat me like an outlaw</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-i-am-happy-people-treat-me-like-an-outlaw.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/when-i-am-happy-people-treat-me-like-an-outlaw.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:43:56+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Today I was in a good mood. A lot of things worked out well and I was genuinely happy. I went to the grocery store and I was approached by other customers as if I worked there. Basically people looked for reasons to communicate with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today I was in a good mood. A lot of things worked out well and I was genuinely happy. I went to the grocery store and I was approached by other customers as if I worked there. Basically people looked for reasons to communicate with me.<br><br>Then I approached a woman, and she was psyched.<br><br>Then I met the postman who was smiling at me and left happy.<br><br>The thing is: I am rarely happy. Most times, things are bad and pull me down. And I can definitely not rely on people on the outside to lift me up, because they are all depressed in this city. The times I wanted mental support are countless, nobody was there for me. I pulled myself out, and now everyone feels entitled to leech.<br><br>So when I am in a good mood, people do not want to multiply it, they want to take it. I feel it, after interacting with a few people, my mood deteriorates.<br><br>And once those leeches sucked it out of me and I would need a refill, NOBODY is there anymore.<br><br>Of course, when I am in a good mood, it is hard to reject people.<br><br>But once I am in a good mood, people pile up, with no decency, no respect of privacy, ready for the taking.<br><br>I don't know what to do with that. Disallow myself to be happy? Stupid idea. Wear T-Shirts with "Not interested"? Funny, but not effective, rather the opposite. Maybe: "I talk to you, you don't talk to me".</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why fight?</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-fight.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-fight.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:43:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What do I mean by this? If you learn martial arts with sparring, despite protection you will suffer injuries. Sometimes to the head, concussions. It is well known that this should be avoided. I was bullied and my physical weakness was an invitation for bullies,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What do I mean by this?<br><br>If you learn martial arts with sparring, despite protection you will suffer injuries. Sometimes to the head, concussions.<br><br>It is well known that this should be avoided.<br><br>I was bullied and my physical weakness was an invitation for bullies, as it always is. I was told violence was wrong and I should ignore the bullies, as most people are told by clueless or vicious others.<br><br>Then I turned towards martial arts, the only thing that made sense a bit, hoping to find confidence, as it's often advertised.<br><br>What I mainly got was being beaten up - first by bullies, then by people in the gym.<br><br>I started to believe that I was training in the wrong gym, the wrong martial art, as some people in forums claim.<br><br>I then attended every dojo in the book in almost all martial arts.<br><br>It is the same everywhere I went to. My conclusion is, those people claiming that everything but their art was at fault are subject to the true scotsman fallacy.<br><br>I met people reporting they had constant headaches after practising longer in martial arts.<br><br>So I could practise longer, hoping I might be able to switch from being beaten up to beating up and endure not only concussions in the long run just for the faint promise of being more self confident. But then, should I reach this, I have to continue practising. Once I stop, fears creep in again.<br><br>And for bullies/attackers in groups, martial artists have nothing going for them. The police looks away, as they always do or request the VICTIM to exactly describe because all surrounding surveillance was disabled just the very moment it happened. And in front of court the victim has to prove everything and even if you are being believed, the punishments are pathetic.<br><br>It is a never ending carousell of injustice and lack of safety.<br><br>And all of that because I wasn't born with strong genes to a society that SHOULD protect me from people like that, but doesn't, that doesn't allow me to carry weapons to even the playing field while having no problem invading my property should I dare to not pay the taxes they need to sustain this shithole of a country(germany). And due to corona I cannot even leave it. And if I could, due to the huge lack of good information, I wouldn't even know where to go.<br><br>So if you practise martial arts without sparring, you are not prepared. If you do with sparring, you get injured. You cannot carry weapons due to the state's regulations that do not protect you in practise.<br><br>Why fight? What for? Concussions? A faint promise of self confidence? The joy of winning a competition just to lose the next?<br><br>I came to the conclusion that learning how to fight is a stupid endeavour that does you more harm than good. That it's more important to learn proven tactics to harm your opponents without risking injury. To take the metaphorical sniper route.<br><br>For exercise health wise, I rather attend a gym.<br><br>But then, you are in a public setting, talk to a woman and some guy, ready to fight and oblivious to the law due to previous 6 beers aims at you, because he wants her too....<br><br>Summary:<br><br>I am interested in your approach to solve this complex problem I described in my post if you have a solution. I prefer private messages due to the higher quality of those, but you can post here aswell.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why I dislike Zombie Shooters</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-dislike-zombie-shooters.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-dislike-zombie-shooters.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:43:18+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Day Z, Dying Light, Left 4 Dead 2. They all are about killing zombies. But zombies are just infected humans. That does nothing to me emotionally. But when there is an elaborately crafted enemy as in the evil within or silent hill, I am all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Day Z, Dying Light, Left 4 Dead 2. They all are about killing zombies. But zombies are just infected humans. That does nothing to me emotionally. But when there is an elaborately crafted enemy as in the evil within or silent hill, I am all for it.<br><br>But zombies? Meh. It's like those ice princess toon that is being shoved into girls throats left and right. The creators had way too much marketing money and decided: WE WILL FORCE THE PEOPLE TO LIKE IT. The ice princess and zombies are both just stupid characters. Compare that to the batman's joker, be it in gotham or one of the movies. Now there went some work in it. But zombies.... There are hardly any games without zombies which might be the reason why people are buying that uncreative shit, might be the reason they have to pile them up because one zombie would be too obviously bland.<br><br>TL/DR: Zombies are not elaboratively crafted compared to even the simplest enemy in non-zombie games. Also, nobody asked for zombies, but as there is a lack of games, people started playing zombie games. Which made developers think people liked it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why I hate strategy games like railway empire</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-hate-strategy-games-like-railway-empire.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-hate-strategy-games-like-railway-empire.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:43:04+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You have it hard to get started. You have to learn how to play. Then all kinds of events make it hard to win, there is always something that doesn't work and soon you are out of money. This bugs me the most. There is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You have it hard to get started. You have to learn how to play.<br><br>Then all kinds of events make it hard to win, there is always something that doesn't work and soon you are out of money.<br><br>This bugs me the most.<br><br>There is just no path what to do.<br><br>You should do X but then some competitor comes in and sabotages your trains.<br><br>You have to sabotage his to then lose money on spies, when you should create new routes to other cities.<br><br>Then you are out of money and some other event makes it even harder to gain money.<br><br>And this is on purpose by the developers. Don't they know that you can only do one thing at once? Multitasking does not work.<br><br>I experience no dopamine when playing those games.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why I hate the PU-Community II</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-hate-the-pu-community-ii.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/why-i-hate-the-pu-community-ii.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:42:47+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What I have been missing the most in the pickup community - actually everywhere on the internet - is someone to take me seriously when I share how I feel about women: I walk around and all I see are women that only go out&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What I have been missing the most in the pickup community - actually everywhere on the internet - is someone to take me seriously when I share how I feel about women:<br><br>I walk around and all I see are women that only go out to "meet men", when in fact they don't meet men. They just put themselves there, surrounded by other females to wait for men to come to them to then select. Then they throw shittests at you but hey because they are women it's all fine.<br>They cannot help it. But we, oh we shouldn't be such pussies, they are just women. We shouldn't get mad.<br><br>Then this shitty "oh, you have to have a feeling of abundance". And this cunt? What does she do? Nothing, she can be needy as fuck and nobody blames her because, oh it's a woman, she cannot help it.<br><br>Like you treat disabled people. "Oh he takes the short bus, it's okay if he hits you, he cannot help it. But YOU, you are fully responsible for your actions if you hit back".<br><br>"Oh it gets to you getting the rolling eyes when you talk to her, something she could never pull off herself? You are such a pathetic fuck."<br><br>"Oh she tells you about her boyfriend, hey move on, some faggot who met her before you is way more important than you are. Know your place or I beat you up."<br><br>"Before you can talk to women, love yourself, you can only feel abundance if you love yourself. But I won't define what that actually means, I just tell you, that you don't get laid if you don't have it."<br><br>And maybe that information makes me hate women more than I would before.<br><br>I used to believe that I just wasn't supposed to get laid. I did everything except it. Then I heard that I could change it, but I couldn't. Then I read posts of asshole people claiming that they got laid using pickup and I am back again in this fucking shit.<br><br>If I at least wasn't the only one to talk like that. Everyone on those fucking pickup forums is so fucking enlightened.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>You are too soft</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Breakfaster</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/you-are-too-soft.html"/>
        <id>https://erfolgreichcharismatisch.github.io/tenants-for-breakfast/you-are-too-soft.html</id>

        <updated>2021-10-08T20:42:28+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Leave her better than you found her(Also written on a toilet btw.) Negs are supposed to make her laugh and feel good Give her a compliment(Direct Game) I wondered why women don't take me seriously till I noticed that PU-literature teaches you to be&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
<li>Leave her better than you found her(Also written on a toilet btw.)</li>
<li>Negs are supposed to make her laugh and feel good</li>
<li>Give her a compliment(Direct Game)</li>
</ul>
<p>I wondered why women don't take me seriously till I noticed that PU-literature teaches you to be soft.<br><br>All of that does neither scare her nor force her to make a decision. It's like this: if it is an even playing field and you are good enough, just like the next guy who happened to be ripped, something you are not, it would work out without pickup. But it doesn't. So you have to even the playing field. With "nieceties"? What about "nice guys don't get laid"?<br><br>Women lie like there's no tomorrow. They enjoy a conversation just to say "Okay bye".<br><br>Something is totally off with pickup advice and it's not what people say in those "what's wrong with pickup" videos.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
